Maybe he was busy
writing clumsy penis metaphors...
...about my fiancée.
(Raj:)Screw you. That was
a beautifully-written penis metaphor.
(Penny:)You know what?
Guys, I'm not in the mood for paintball.
(Leonard:)- What do you say we just bag it?
- Fine.
- Sure, whatever.
- But you can't quit.
That's a court-martial offense.
That's punishable by...
(Sheldon:)You can't quit.
I'm sorry, Sheldon, it's just
not a good time for playing games.
(Sheldon:)This is a game to you?
(Sheldon:)Uh, was the Battle of Antietam
a game, huh?
(Sheldon:)Was the Sack of Rome a game?
(Leonard:)Yes, no and no.
(Sheldon:)Wait.
(Sheldon:)I just want you all to know
that I forgive you.
This mutiny isn't your fauIt.
(Sheldon:)It's mine.
(Sheldon:)I haven't earned these bars.